A Guide to the U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission Yucca Mountain Research Collection TD898.12.N3 U85
University of Nevada, Reno. DeLaMare Science & Engineering Library
- "Contract (FIN) A-1756." (Box 181, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1756." (Box 181, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1756." (Box 181, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1756." (Box 181, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1756." (Box 181, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1756." (Box 182, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1756." (Box 182, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1756." (Box 182, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1756." (Box 182, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1756." (Box 182, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1756." (Box 182, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1756." (Box 182, Folder 7)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1757." (Box 183, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1757." (Box 183, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1757." (Box 183, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-1757." (Box 183, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3163." (Box 183, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 184, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 184, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 184, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 184, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 184, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 184, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 185, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 185, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 185, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 185, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 185, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 185, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 186, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 186, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3164." (Box 186, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3167." (Box 187, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3167." (Box 187, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3167." (Box 187, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3167." (Box 187, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3167." (Box 187, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3167." (Box 188, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3167." (Box 188, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3167." (Box 188, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3167." (Box 188, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3167." (Box 188, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3167." (Box 189, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3167." (Box 189, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-3168." (Box 189, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4165." (Box 190, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4165." (Box 190, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4165." (Box 190, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4165." (Box 190, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4165." (Box 190, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4165." (Box 191, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4165." (Box 191, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4165." (Box 191, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4165." (Box 191, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4165." (Box 191, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4167." (Box 192, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4167." (Box 192, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4167." (Box 192, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4167." (Box 192, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4167." (Box 192, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4167." (Box 192, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4170." (Box 193, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4171." (Box 193, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) A-4171." (Box 193, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) A-7150." (Box 193, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 194, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 194, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 194, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 194, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 195, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 195, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 195, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 195, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 195, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 196, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 196, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 196, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 196, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 196, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 197, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 197, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 197, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 197, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 197, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 198, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 198, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 198, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0287." (Box 198, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0288." (Box 199, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0288." (Box 199, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0288." (Box 199, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0288." (Box 199, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0288." (Box 199, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0288." (Box 200, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0288." (Box 200, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0289." (Box 200, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0289." (Box 200, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0290." (Box 201, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0290." (Box 201, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0290." (Box 201, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0290." (Box 201, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0290." (Box 201, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0290." (Box 202, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0290." (Box 202, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0290." (Box 202, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0290." (Box 202, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0290." (Box 202, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0290." (Box 202, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0290." (Box 203, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0290." (Box 203, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-0290." (Box 203, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-3109." (Box 203, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6932." (Box 203, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6934." (Box 203, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6934." (Box 203, Folder 7)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6934." (Box 204, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6934." (Box 204, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6934." (Box 204, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6934." (Box 204, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6934." (Box 204, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6935." (Box 205, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6935." (Box 205, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6983." (Box 205, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6983." (Box 205, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6983." (Box 205, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 206, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 206, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 206, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 206, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 206, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 207, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 207, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 207, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 207, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 207, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." 1 of 2. (Box 208, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." 2 of 2. (Box 208, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 208, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 208, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." 1 of 2. (Box 209, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." 2 of 2. (Box 209, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 209, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 210, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 210, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 210, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6985." (Box 210, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6986." (Box 211, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6986." (Box 211, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6986." (Box 211, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6986." (Box 211, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-6986." (Box 211, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7327." (Box 212, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7327." (Box 212, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7327." (Box 212, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7328." (Box 212, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7328." (Box 212, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7328." (Box 213, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7328." (Box 213, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7328." (Box 213, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7328." (Box 213, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7328." (Box 213, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7328." (Box 214, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7328." (Box 214, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7328." (Box 214, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7328." (Box 214, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7328." (Box 214, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7328." (Box 214, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7328." (Box 214, Folder 7)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7373." (Box 215, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7389." (Box 215, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7389." (Box 215, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7389." (Box 215, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7389." (Box 216, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7389." (Box 216, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7389." (Box 216, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7389." (Box 216, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7389." (Box 216, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7390." (Box 217, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7390." (Box 217, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7390." (Box 217, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) B-7390." (Box 217, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1003." (Box 218, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1003." (Box 218, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1003." (Box 218, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1003." (Box 218, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1003." (Box 218, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1003." (Box 218, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1004." (Box 219, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1004." (Box 219, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1004." (Box 219, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1004." (Box 219, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1004." (Box 220, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1004." (Box 220, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1004." (Box 220, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1010." (Box 220, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1014." (Box 220, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1014." (Box 220, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1016." (Box 221, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1016." (Box 221, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1016." (Box 221, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1016." (Box 221, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1016." (Box 221, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1018." (Box 221, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1018." (Box 221, Folder 7)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1020." (Box 222, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1020." (Box 222, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1020." (Box 222, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1020." (Box 222, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1020." (Box 222, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1020." (Box 222, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1020." (Box 222, Folder 7)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1021." (Box 223, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1021." (Box 223, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1021." (Box 223, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1021." (Box 223, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1021." (Box 223, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1021." (Box 224, Folder 1)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1021." (Box 224, Folder 2)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1021." (Box 224, Folder 3)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1021." (Box 224, Folder 4)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1021." (Box 224, Folder 5)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1035." (Box 224, Folder 6)
- "Contract (FIN) D-1036." (Box 224, Folder 7)
- "Cumulative accession list contract files related to project WM-11." (Box 225, Folder 1)
- "Cumulative accession list contract files related to project WM-11." (Box 225, Folder 2)
- "Cumulative accession list contract files related to project WM-11." (Box 225, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Local public document room directory." NUREG/BR-0088 Rev. 2. (Box 226, Folder 1)
- "Nuclear documents system/advanced design (NUDOCS/AD)." (Box 226, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Local public document room directory." NUREG/BR-0088., undated (Box 226, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commision. "U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission staff meetings open to the public weekly announcement." (Box 226, Folder 4)
- U.S. NRC Local Public Document Room Program. "LPDR update." (Box 226, Folder 5)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Nuclear documents system advanced design version 002.000." (Box 226, Folder 6)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Responsiveness to the public: draft report for comment." (Box 227, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Local public document room directory." NUREG/BR-0088 Rev. 2. (Box 227, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Public document room file classification system." NUREG/BR-0052 Rev. 2. (Box 227, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Information digest 1996 edition." NUREG-1350 volume 8. (Box 227, Folder 4)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Information digest 1997 edition." NUREG-1350 volume 9. (Box 227, Folder 5)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Information digest 1998 edition." (Box 227, Folder 6)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Citizen's guide to U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission information." NUREG/BR-0010 Rev. 3. (Box 227, Folder 7)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Citizen's guide to U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission information." NUREG/BR-0010 Rev. 2. (Box 227, Folder 8)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Annual report 1992." NUREG-1145 vol. 9. (Box 227, Folder 9)
- U.S. Congress, Office of Technology Assessment. "Aging nuclear power plants: Managing plant life and decommissioning." (Box 227, Folder 10)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "NRC regulator of nuclear safety." NUREG/BR-0164. (Box 227, Folder 11)
- Walker, J.S. "A short history of nuclear regulation, 1946-1990." U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. (Box 227, Folder 12)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Public document room user's guide." NUREG/BR-0004 rev. 2. (Box 227, Folder 13)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Directory of contacts for technical issues." NUREG/BR-0120 rev. 1. (Box 227, Folder 14)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Atoms to electricity." DOE/NE-0085. (Box 227, Folder 15)
- National Archives and Records Administration. "Code of federal regulations: Energy 10 - parts 0 to 50." (Box 227, Folder 16)
- National Archives and Records Administration. "Code of federal regulations: Energy 10 - parts 51 to 199." (Box 227, Folder 17)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide series division 1 - power reactors: Table of Contents." (Box 228, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 1.1-1.50." (Box 228, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 1.51-1.69." (Box 228, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 1.70." (Box 228, Folder 4)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 1.71-1.81." (Box 228, Folder 5)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 1.89-1.99." (Box 228, Folder 6)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 1.100-1.109." (Box 229, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 1.110." (Box 229, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 1.111-1.114." (Box 229, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 1.115-1.125." (Box 229, Folder 4)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 1.126-1.143." (Box 229, Folder 5)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 1.144-1.156." (Box 229, Folder 6)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 2.1-3.24." (Box 229, Folder 7)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 3.25-3.34." (Box 230, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 3.35-3.43." (Box 230, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 3.44." (Box 230, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 3.45-3.50." (Box 230, Folder 4)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 3.51-3.63." (Box 230, Folder 5)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 4.15-5.25." (Box 231, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 5.26-5.44." (Box 231, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 5.45-5.51." (Box 231, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 5.52." (Box 231, Folder 4)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 5.53-5.55." (Box 231, Folder 5)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 5.56-5.63." (Box 232, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 6.1-8.20." (Box 232, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 8.21-10.7." (Box 232, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Regulatory guide 10.8-10.11." (Box 232, Folder 4)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Standard review plan for the review of safety analysis reports for nuclear power plants LWR edition." Introduction to 2.4.11-9. (Box 233, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Standard review plan for the review of safety analysis reports for nuclear power plants LWR edition." 2.4.12 to 2.5.512. (Box 233, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Standard review plan for the review of safety analysis reports for nuclear power plants LWR edition." 3.2.1 to 3.5.3-7. (Box 233, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Standard review plan for the review of safety analysis reports for nuclear power plants LWR edition." 3.6 to 3.7.4-8. (Box 233, Folder 4)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Standard review plan for the review of safety analysis reports for nuclear power plants LWR edition." 3.8 to 3.11-8. (Box 233, Folder 5)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Standard review plan for the review of safety analysis reports for nuclear power plants LWR edition." 5.9 to 8-7. (Box 233, Folder 6)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Standard review plan for the review of safety analysis reports for nuclear power plants LWR edition." 9 to 15-16. (Box 233, Folder 7)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Low temperature thermal treatment (LT3®) technology Roy F. Weston, Inc.: Applications analysis report." EPA/540/AR-92/019. (Box 234, Folder 1)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Toronto Harbor Commissioners (THC) soil recycle treatment train: Applications analysis report." EPA/540/AR-93/517. (Box 234, Folder 2)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Resources Conservation Company B.E.S.T.® solvent extraction technology: Applications analysis report." EPA/540/AR-92/079. (Box 234, Folder 3)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Accutech pneumatic fracturing extraction and hot gas injection, phase I: Applications analysis report." EPA/540/AR-93/509. (Box 234, Folder 4)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Membrane treatment of wood preserving site groundwater by SPB Technologies, Inc.: Applications analysis report." EPA/540/AR-92/014. (Box 234, Folder 5)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "CWM PO*WW*ER™ evaporation-catalytic oxidation technology: Applications analysis report." EPA/540/AR-93/506. (Box 234, Folder 6)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "BIOGENESIS™ soil washing technology: Innovative technology evaluation report." EPA/540/R-93/510. (Box 234, Folder 7)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "EPA RREL's mobile volume reduction unit: Applications analysis report." EPA/540/AR-93/508. (Box 234, Folder 8)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Hydraulic fracturing technology: Applications analysis and technology evaluation report." EPA/540/R-93/505. (Box 234, Folder 9)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "The superfund innovative technology evaluation program: Annual report to congress 1992." EPA/540/R-93/525. (Box 234, Folder 10)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Eco logic international gas-phase chemical reduction process - the thermal desorption unit: Applications analysis report." EPA/540/AR-94/504. (Box 234, Folder 11)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "Eco logic international gas-phase chemical reduction process - the reactor system: Application analysis report." EPA/540/AR-93/522. (Box 234, Folder 12)
- U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "BESCORP soil washing system for lead battery site treatment: Applications analysis report." EPA/540/AR-93/503. (Box 234, Folder 13)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Information notices." (Box 234, Folder 14)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "Clarification of TMI action plan requirements." NUREG-0737. (Box 234, Folder 15)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "NRC action plan developed as a result of the TMI-2 accident." NUREG-0660 vol. 1. (Box 234, Folder 16)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "NRC action plan developed as a result of the TMI-2 accident." NUREG-0660 vol. 2. (Box 234, Folder 17)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Draft environmental impact statement: Management of commercially generated radioactive waste." DOE/EIS-0046-D vol. 2. (Box 235, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Environmental aspects of commercial radioactive waste management." DOE/ET-0029 vol. 1. (Box 235, Folder 2)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Technology for commercial radioactive waste management." DOE/ET-0028 vol. 1. (Box 236, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Technology for commercial radioactive waste management." DOE/ET-0028 vol. 2. (Box 236, Folder 2)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Technology for commercial radioactive waste management." DOE/ET-0028 vol. 3. (Box 236, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Technology for commercial radioactive waste management." DOE/ET-0028 vol. 4. (Box 237, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of Energy. "Technology for commercial radioactive waste management." DOE/ET-0028 vol. 5. (Box 237, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "NRC staff site characterization analysis of the Department of Energy's site characterization plan, Yucca Mountain Site, Nevada." Introduction to ch. 3. (Box 238, Folder 1)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "NRC staff site characterization analysis of the Department of Energy's site characterization plan, Yucca Mountain Site, Nevada." Ch. 4, pp. 4-1 to 4-132. (Box 238, Folder 2)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "NRC staff site characterization analysis of the Department of Energy's site characterization plan, Yucca Mountain Site, Nevada." Ch. 4, pp. 4-133 to 4-316. (Box 238, Folder 3)
- U.S. Nuclear Regulatory Commission. "NRC staff site characterization analysis of the Department of Energy's site characterization plan, Yucca Mountain Site, Nevada." Appendices. (Box 238, Folder 4)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Office of Civilian Radioactive Waste Management. "Site characterization plan Yucca Mountain Site, Nevada research and development area, Nevada." DOE/RW-0199. Vol. I, part A: Table of contents. (Box 239, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Office of Civilian Radioactive Waste Management. "Site characterization plan Yucca Mountain Site, Nevada research and development area, Nevada." DOE/RW-0199. Vol. I, part A: Introduction. (Box 239, Folder 2)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Office of Civilian Radioactive Waste Management. "Site characterization plan Yucca Mountain Site, Nevada research and development area, Nevada." DOE/RW-0199. Vol. I, part A: Part A, mined geologic disposal system. (Box 239, Folder 3)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Office of Civilian Radioactive Waste Management. "Site characterization plan Yucca Mountain Site, Nevada research and development area, Nevada." DOE/RW-0199. Vol. I, part A: Chapter 1, geology. (Box 239, Folder 4)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Office of Civilian Radioactive Waste Management. "Site characterization plan Yucca Mountain Site, Nevada research and development area, Nevada." DOE/RW-0199. Vol. I, part A: Chapter 2, geoengineering. (Box 239, Folder 5)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Office of Civilian Radioactive Waste Management. "Site characterization plan Yucca Mountain Site, Nevada research and development area, Nevada." DOE/RW-0199. Vol. II, part A: Table of contents. (Box 240, Folder 1)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Office of Civilian Radioactive Waste Management. "Site characterization plan Yucca Mountain Site, Nevada research and development area, Nevada." DOE/RW-0199. Vol. II, part A: Ch. 3, hydrology. (Box 240, Folder 2)
- U.S. Department of Energy, Office of Civilian Radioactive Waste Management. "Site characterization plan Yucca Mountain Site, Nevada research and development area, Nevada." DOE/RW-0199. Vol. II, part A: Ch. 4, geochemistry. (Box 240, Folder 3)